darkthrone.com 2005-12-12

# Dark Throne (beta) Privacy

**Overview**

Lazarus Software is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of registered users of and of visitors to its sites. We want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for our registered players and visitors, and in particular, ensure that kids' information is protected. 

The purpose of this Dark Throne privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcomed visitor or registered member of Dark Throne, (1) what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit Dark Throne; (2) how we may use that information; (3) whether we disclose it to anyone; and (4) the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. 

Lazarus Software welcomes comments and questions on this policy. Lazarus Software is dedicated to protecting your personal information. Due to the rapidly evolving nature of the technologies, we may occasionally update this policy. Notice of any revisions will be posted to this site. Any comments or questions regarding our privacy practices should be sent to [privacy@lazarussoft.com](mailto:privacy@lazarussoft.com).

**What personal information does Dark Throne collect?**

Lazarus Software collects personally identifying information during: (i) game signup; (ii) user surveys; 

In addition, we collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, aggregate information about which pages visitors access, user-specific information about which pages visitors access and how much time is spent in particular areas, and information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information and/or information provided in site registration forms, including but not limited to a visitor's name, address, and phone number. 

**What does Dark Throne do with the information it collects?**

Lazarus Software may use personally identifying information of its visitors to award prizes, track compliance with our Rules of Conduct, Anti-Spam policy, or for editorial purposes (to the extent that is explained when visitors provide the information). 

When you create a user profile or participate in interactive areas of Dark Throne, including the message center, forum, and chat room, all information volunteered by you is displayed or broadcast publicly to the Dark Throne community and/or to the chat room that you are visiting. You should keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - in a user profile or in chat areas, for example - that information can be collected and used by others who visit that area of our site. 

**How will Dark Throne protect your personal information?**

Lazarus Software will take appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us. Whenever you give Lazarus Software sensitive information (home address, for instance), Lazarus Software will take commercially reasonable steps to make sure your information is secure. 

Lazarus Software WILL NOT share any personal information of its users to advertisers or any third party companies.

**How to update personal information**

You can help Lazarus Software to maintain the accuracy of your information by notifying us of any change to your address, title, phone number, or e-mail address. If at any time you wish to modify your information or stop receiving communications from Lazarus Software or Dark Throne, you can contact Lazarus Software through e-mail at [privacy@lazarussoft.com](mailto:privacy@lazarussoft.com). Please include your e-mail address and account username in the message. 

**Policies for individuals under 13**

Lazarus Software encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children (persons under the age of 13 years old) and to participate in the interactive activities offered on our service. No information should be submitted to or posted at Dark Throne by visitors under 13 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. 

**Use of cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your passwords and preferences while you're at our site. The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you'll find them at most major Web sites. 

Dark Throne does not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. Lazarus Software does not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, nor is that information shared with any third parties whatsoever. 

You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. Lazarus Software does not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to the Dark Throne cookie policy. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. 

By using this site, you signify your assent to the Dark Throne Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of Dark Throne following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Any comments or questions regarding our privacy practices should be sent to [privacy@lazarussoft.com](mailto:privacy@lazarussoft.com).
